downloadnew.org 2011-04-15

# Privacy Policy - DownloadNew.org

When a visitor requests pages from DownloadNew.org site, our Web servers automatically recognize the browser's domain name, and IP address. Our server do not record e-mail addresses. We collect the domain names and IP addresses in order to aggregate information on the pages users access or visit. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals. From time to time, we may ask users to provide an e-mail address or mailing address for the purpose of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters). Whenever the identity of a visitor is recorded, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the request before the information is requested. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example advertiser such as Google AdSense). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Please refer to the privacy policies of the network for details. 

Google Adsense uses cookies, including DoubleClick DART cookie and/or web beacons to collect information from our visitors while serving ads to our website. This relates to Google AdSense advertisers' use of innovative products and features like Gadget Ads and other offerings in the future. 

**SECURITY**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Firefox and Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. 

**LINKS**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we DownloadNew.org, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
